{
  "name": "Reizināšana ar 4",
  "level": 1,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 25,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 4 × 1?",
      "correctAnswer": 4,
      "options": [3, 4, 5, 6]
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 4 × 2?",
      "correctAnswer": 8,
      "options": [6, 7, 8, 9]
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 4 × 3?",
      "correctAnswer": 12,
      "options": [10, 11, 12, 13]
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 4 × 4?",
      "correctAnswer": 16,
      "options": [14, 15, 16, 17]
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 4 × 5?",
      "correctAnswer": 20,
      "options": [18, 19, 20, 21]
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 4 × 6?",
      "correctAnswer": 24,
      "options": [22, 23, 24, 25]
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 4 × 7?",
      "correctAnswer": 28,
      "options": [26, 27, 28, 29]
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 4 × 8?",
      "correctAnswer": 32,
      "options": [30, 31, 32, 33]
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 4 × 9?",
      "correctAnswer": 36,
      "options": [34, 35, 36, 37]
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 4 × 10?",
      "correctAnswer": 40,
      "options": [38, 39, 40, 41]
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 4 × 11?",
      "correctAnswer": 44,
      "options": [42, 43, 44, 45]
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 4 × 12?",
      "correctAnswer": 48,
      "options": [46, 47, 48, 49]
    }
  ]
}
